canadafreepress.com 2018-10-05

# CFP Privacy Statement

* * *

[

#### Subscribe to Canada Free Press for FREE

](http://www.subscribepage.com/g4c3q7)

Canada Free Press Privacy Policies

This statement may be updated from time-to-time and was last updated, August 15, 2004.

We at Canada Free Press are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of your personal information.

Collection, use and disclosure of personal information by the Canada Free Press are governed by the _Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act_ and any applicable provincial legislation. That Privacy Code explains what personal information can be collected and how it can be used.

Personal information is any information about an identifiable individual. Personal information does not include the name, title, business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization. 

Information used solely for journalistic, literary or artistic purposes is exempted from the Act as is demographic statistics about Free Press customers, number of visitors, and average time spent on the website.

Our web site does not collect "cookies" which are text files which are usually meant to store your personal preferences for particular web sites, such as language, favourite pages, etcetera. One exception to this is our Pulse Poll, which is provided by a third-party as an offsite service, which uses a cookie to prevent people from voting more than once.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

We are not responsible for the policies of third-party websites we link to and those other sites may not be subject to a privacy code or the Act. Also, such links are not to be deemed as endorsements of those websites or of any products on those sites.

Those purchasing services from us through PayPal can read their stringent privacy policy statement at [http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside](https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)

We will never sell or rent your personally identifiable information or a list of our customers to third parties.

Those who sign up for our update service can rest assured that your e-mail address is kept confidential and only used for the update mailings.

Other than the mailing list, or for journalist purposes, Canada Free Press shall limit its collection of personal information, to that which is collected by fair and lawful means necessary, such as banking details and credit history to assess the credit risk of advertisers and do maintain the right to pass on that information to credit bureaus and collection agencies in the case of outstanding accounts not paid.

If you have questions about this privacy policy or an inquiry about any information we may or do have on file please write to:

Privacy Officer

Canada Free Press

* * *
